onestatfree.com 2019-07-19

# OneStat Free hit and web counter

| 

To protect your privacy, OneStat.com has instituted policies that give you information and control.

|  |   
---  
  
OneStat Free

OneStat Free is the best free hit counter available. It is password protected, has the ability to track unlimited web pages and tells you everything about your visitors and web site. 100% Free!  

OneStat Platinum 

Advanced web analytics for marketers who want to track visitor behavior, online advertising campaigns and measure Return on Investment in detail. Professional web site statistics software developed for medium to large web sites. Pricing starts at $ 1810, 1038 GBP or 1500 Euro per year for up to 1 million pageviews per month.  

OneStat Premium 

Professional web metrics software for SME, providing detailed analysis about unique visitors, site navigation paths, search engines traffic and geographic origin of visitors. True value for money, with prices starting at $275, 150 GBP or 220 Euro per year.  

OneStat Adworks 

The most comprehensive web analytics tool for measuring and tracking the ROI of online advertising and marketing campaigns like banner advertising, text links, Google Adwords®, Yahoo Search Marketing and other PPC campaigns. Low priced at $467, 260 GBP or 375 Euro per year.  
  
---  
  
Testimonials

I must tell you that I'm stunned by the high level of this site. You have truly a done a wonderful job here, and there is no doubt that this is the best free hit counter of the web.

_Our compliments to your hit counter service. First we thought 'no not another counter' . But your web site statistics are different. A very good look and feel and the service is fast and reliable._

This is a very nice offer and 100 percent free, amazing! A really good piece of programming and the best web analytics service I know. Thanks!  
  
---  
  
Advertising

Do you want to advertise at the OneStatFree.com web site and reach over 100,000 webmasters and site owners? Promote your company with a text link on our home page. Go to our [contact page](http://www.onestat.com/html/contactus.html) for more information about pricing.   
  
Our privacy statement covers:

  1. OneStat.com provides a link to this Privacy Statement on all pages that ask for personal information
  2. OneStat.com will not release personal identifying information about you without first obtaining consent 
  3. The information we collect
  4. Our use of your information
  5. How to change or deactivate your information

When you visit an OneStat.com Client Web Site, we may collect general information that will not personally identify you, such as:

  * Internet browser
  * Operating system
  * Date of visit
  * Time of visit
  * Path taken through the site

This information alone does not identify an individual and we will not combine it with information that does identify you as an individual. It provides statistics that we use to analyze and improve OneStat.com Client Web Sites. Through this "Aggregate Statistical Data," we are able to gain insights and a greater understanding of how people use our client Web sites.

Personally identifiable information is defined as any personal information that could identify you, such as your name, address, telephone number, billing and shipping information, credit card information, or e-mail address. In general, when you visit a OneStat.com Client Web Site, you do not have to tell us who you are, or reveal any personally identifiable information. Because we take your privacy seriously, we will not collect any personally identifiable information unless you voluntarily provide it. At no time during your visit to a OneStat.com Client Web Site should you feel obligated to reveal any personal information to OneStat.com. We may share your personal information with third party suppliers and service providers, including independent contractors providing services for, or with OneStat.com. In all cases, these third parties are contractually required to keep that information confidential. They are not authorized by OneStat.com to use that information for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for, or with OneStat.com. We may also disclose personally identifiable information to third parties if you consent to the disclosure, if we are compelled or authorized to do so by law, or if we reasonably believe there is a threat to someone's life or health. Personally identifiable information submitted for employment purposes will only be used in connection with the application process. It will not be used or disclosed for any other purposes unless required or authorized by law. 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and demographic information (like their zip code). 

We may use customer contact information from the registration form to:

  1. send you information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners and
  2. contact you when necessary

You may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

We may use "cookies" to gather statistical information that helps us understand what you find interesting and useful on our client Web sites. These cookies are known as your "Unique Visitor Cookie" and identify you only by random number (e.g. #12489). You can decline our cookies by adjusting the "accept cookies" setting on your browser, however this may affect the functionality of OneStat.com Client Web Sites. We may also embed a piece of code into pages of certain client Web sites. This gives us statistical site usage information about the pages visited, duration of page view, location previous to accessing the OneStat.com Client Web Site, the navigational habits of user, and browser and operating system. We do not use this code to collect any personally identifiable information.

This site contains links to other sites. OneStat.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of Web sites to which we link. We have special business relationships with some companies, but none of them receive individual identifying information about you collected at OneStat.com.

We are committed to maintaining the security of the data we collect and protecting it from loss, misuse, or alteration. This applies to demographic information, client site usage information, and personally identifiable information. We store the data collected on secure OneStat.com servers that can be accessed only by authorized OneStat.com personnel To safeguard all information collected, OneStat.com and all of its employees follow the practices in this policy. No one is permitted to access or use information for any purpose other than those explained in this policy.

If you would like to change or deactivate the information you have submitted, please send a request to privacy@OneStat.com. OneStat.com will change or de-activate any information that could be used to identify you as soon as possible after your request, unless there we are required or authorized by law not to do so. Once de-activated your data will not be accessible, however due to limitations imposed by system backups to magnetic media, including the off site secure storage of data from our data warehouse your data can in some circumstances remain on these tapes. In the unlikely event that one of these tapes is accessed as part of a larger recovery of OneStat.com data, your data would continue to be flagged and remain de-activated and inaccessible for use by OneStat.com staff.

To fully protect your privacy, we reserve the right to amend this policy at any time, and for any reason. We will post the amended terms on this Web site as they occur and encourage you to frequently check for updates.

Nothing contained in this policy is intended to create a contract or agreement between OneStat.com and any user providing identifiable information in any form, whether visiting this site or any OneStat.com client site. We will take all necessary steps to comply with this privacy policy, however, to the extent permitted by law, nothing in this policy is intended to hold OneStat.com liable for any failure to comply with this policy. Further, because OneStat.com does not control the privacy practices of our clients, we advise that you read and fully understand their privacy policies.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: privacy@OneStat.com
